Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are up, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
That creature, it's a slime, isn't it?
A what?
I thought that slimes were limited to
the realm of fantasy, but apparently not.
I read a book about a slime, and
it looked just like that one.
There's nothing else it could be.
The book was quite fascinating.
I couldn't put it down.
This slime you see loved
to attack beautiful women.
Its body fluids were harmless, but
they had a knack for melting clothes.
Oh, naughty.
That monster is pretty messed up, huh?
Uh, by the way, can I borrow that book?
Could I borrow it, too?
Would you shut up?
Just look.
If that thing touches you, it's going to
do a lot worse than just melt your clothes.
The fish are dying from the little pieces
of itself that dropped in the lake.
The thing's made of poison.
It only takes a drop to kill,
and it looks like it's spreading.
It's poison?
Wait, but the samurai's
torso is in that lake.
Surely not you're diving in, sanji.
I brought him with us, so
I can't let him die here.
I may be a woman right now,
but it's time to man up.
I'm proud of you.
Handle the ones behind you!
I won't be too long. Huh? Behind me?
A veritable puffy of many slimes!
What'd you think in here?
Nami, I'm sorry.
But still, I'm the strongest
swimmer on the crew.
I swear I'll be done before anything
happens to your gorgeous body!
Careful!
Good luck down there!
This is even colder than it looks!
I better make this quick!
Monet's alone.
This is my chance.
Sorry, the Master's not here. Yeah?
Where'd he go?
Probably outside to watch the fight.
That degenerate can't get
enough death and destruction.
That's all right.
I don't need him.
I think I'll be taking off soon.
I've seen everything.
I'm through with this place.
Shame.
It'll be lonely without you.
I could use your help with
something first, though.
Could I borrow you for a sec?
What is this? A date?
Lucky me.
A man of few words, are we? Where to?
You'll see.
All right.
I was bored anyway.
That must be the bird Lady
Usopp was talking about.
Straw Hat caught the master!
Way to go, Luffy!
Little punk, how dare you!
Crazy kid.
Let go, you fool!
So that's Haki.
Caesar has Logia powers, right?
But Luffy can still grab him
even though he's made of gas.
Back off, Straw Hat!
We'll soothe!
Hurry!
Take him out, quick!
If you jerks want to pick a
fight, then pick one with me!
And clutch!
Out of my way!
Luffy's got this one.
Caesar can't use his power.
Not exactly.
I wouldn't celebrate.
With Armament Haki, Luffy
is able to touch Caesar,
even though he has Logia powers.
However, unlike ocean
water or sea prism stone,
it doesn't actually weaken
the person that he touches.
We don't know the full extent
of the Gas-Gasfruit's power.
This is only the beginning.
Don't get cocky, you brat!
Armament hardening!
Nick!
Gum-Gum!
Gas robe!
What's going on here?
I can't get away!
Oop!
Just suck it up and
die already, would you?
I promise it'll be fun!
For me!
Luffy! Dammit!
I've performed countless experiments.
And I can assure you that
my gas will subject you?
to only the most exquisite of suffering.
I think he's lost his mind.
No, Joe, he's done for.
He's sucking up all of it.
He's screwed now.
I'm afraid to watch it.
Neat.
I guess poison doesn't
bother me too much anymore.
Probably because of Magellan.
Magellan?
The prison guard with
the parimethia powers?
My poison's potency makes his look puny!
Now, gong gong!
Get me!
Master!
How dare you!
We won't let you lay
another finger on him!
Mind your own business,
you maggots! Master?
He didn't just call us maggots, did he?
We must have heard him wrong. Gum-Gum!
Let's go!
Gunfire! Gah!
And Dasta Net!
Huffy!
All right, Master!
I think we've had enough fun for
today, wake up my smileys, wake up!
Smileys? Huh?
They're moving, how do they do that?
Very good, now give Straw
Hat a big hug, go! No!
They can follow orders?
I thought they were just goop.
Luffy, run away!
Those slime guys blow up!
Um, woo-wee! Luffy!
It's time to say goodbye!
Gastonet!
Luffy!
He he he!
What?
All right.
Com-com-jecture!
No! Master!
Those slimy dudes blow up like crazy.
Look at that!
Getting us all worked up over nothing!
Muffy's got this in the bag!
I hope so.
Damn, that kid's tough!
Just let him handle this.
Round two!
You gotta fight us too!
If that's what you want, sure!
Okay, I got you for
real this time! Master!
Robin!
Franky!
Is there anything here I can put him in?
He's got Logia power,
so we can't tie him up.
So, like a barrel or something?
Whoa, whoa!
Not so fast!
The Navy is taking him
into custody, so step back!
You might as well turn
yourself in while you're at it!
Hands up, pirate scum!
So what now?
Do we fight the Straw Hats or not?
Straw Hat!
What's wrong?
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Oh, my God.
Show yourself.
Who are you?
It's me.
Why aren't you here?
Why now?
How many years has it been?
Look at you, all grown up.
Long.
You think the boss doesn't
know what's going on?
I had hoped you were smarter than that.
To be honest with you, we don't
trust this Caesar character either.
The guy is shady.
That's why the boss sent an
undercover agent to the island.
The lovely monet here.
Rumor has it, you're a warlord now.
That's one hell of a promotion.
When did you get here?
Fair go.
Actually, I just arrived.
I was spending some time in Dressrosa.
I hitched a ride on a S .A .D.
tanker leaving port And now, it
seems that was the right move
What do you mean by that?
Why target me?
I didn't do a damn thing to you No,
not yet anyway Because if you had,
you'd be dead right now I
hate to break it to you,
but there's no fooling us grown-ups. Law.
Well, in that case, I
should just finish you!
Oh, yeah.
One more thing before I go.
Show some respect, kid.
It's Mr.
Vergo to you.
What the heck happened here?
I got no idea.
What do you think we should do?
He's got Tashigi.
Now, that's Smoker, remember?
You know, I never thought I'd see the Vice
Admiral get knocked out twice in one day.
And he's not the only one who went down.
Three of the Straw Hats did too.
Think the Master used conquerors, Haki?
Don't be ridiculous.
There's no way he could be
that much stronger than them.
Then what was it?
I mean, he beat all of them without
even laying a finger on him.
Well, that was fun while it lasted.
that's what you get maybe you should
have known better than to mess with the
master he is our god of salvation master
master master master
master master now we
mustn't waste any time my strong soldiers
hurry and tie these five pirate scoundrels
up at once you see prism stone shackles
on the power holders once you're done i
want you to move out leave the sailors
behind and seek refuge inside the lab it's
far too dangerous out
here i'm sure you've
all noticed the strange substance that's
been raining down from the sky there's
no cause for concern i will ensure your
safety okay thank you master it seems the
yeti cool brothers failed at their task
Oh, well, I can't blame them.
I guess the combination of Straw Hat and
Law was simply too much for them to handle.
Ah!
Right in the face!
No!
It's poison gas!
My eyes!
Oh, wait.
I don't have any eyes. Guess what?
I'm immune to your attack.
Now fight me to let in this villain.
I'm not again.
Seems we can't use our
swords against them.
They spit poison gas.
Why'd you go and poke the damn thing?
You saw what it did to me.
I thought that maybe it
just didn't like you.
What are we going to do now?
We've got nowhere to run.
Hey, I know.
They're made of jelly, right?
I think you should try eating one.
What? No way!
I wish you'd stop bullying me
into things like this, Zoro!
I'm nearly 70 years older than you!
Fine, sorry I asked.
Never mind Grandpa.
I know you didn't just call me that!
I'm no Grandpa, I'm a lively skeleton!
Whoa, what's wrong with him?
Damn, it's cold.
Sorry about this, Nami.
What's that?
Is it the slime's venom or something?
Oh, that's just great!
Here's hoping the torso is not stuck
in the middle of that poisonous cloud.
I've been using observation Haki for a
while now and I haven't found anything.
It must be getting weak;
I can't tell the difference
between its life force
and the fish that are
swimming around a shark.
Are you kidding me?
Are you feeling all right, Mr. Samurai?
Hey, what's the matter?
You look like you're in pain.
Oh, no, you don't!
You're not getting away from me!
Stop chewing on it, you bastard!
This doesn't hurt, it merely itches a bit!
Jeez, what's gotten into this guy?
It must be dreadful to sound like those.
I'm fine!
Maybe something happened to Sanji?
Let go of it or else, shark!
I've got the last piece
of the samurai puzzle now,
we can put the poor bastard
back together again.
I gotta hurry and get the shore.
Oh, it's closing up!
The poison already got this far?
Now what'll I do?
I'm completely surrounded.
Is Nami's body strong enough
to get me out of this?
I guess there's only one way to find out.
It's not looking good for Sanji.
The whole lake is turning
the color of the poison.
He'd better hurry and come ashore.
Walk!
Don't close up!
He made it out alive! Sure did.
And he's got the torso.
Just like you said he would!
What can I say here?
I feared I would never have
my body back as it should be.
But thanks to you, I'm a
whole samurai once again.
Whoa, I must admit, you're a lot
taller than I expected you to be.
Even taller than me, I believe.
Why, yes, that's true.
Allow me to introduce myself.
Gentlemen, I am the samurai Kidamon.
I hailed from a town called Kuri, in
the land of Wano, if you're not aware.
Can somebody help me out here?
I'm about to freeze to death.
Yes, sorry to keep you waiting.
This should do it.
It's still cold.
That coat's going to disappear
once he takes it off, right?
What shall I call you, curly eyebrow?
I would like to know your
honorable name, my good sir.
Fine, my name is Sanji.
Cut the sir crap, okay?
What, you get your body back and all
of a sudden you start acting like Mr.
Manners?
I put my neck out to help you
when you were just a severed head.
But instead of being appreciative,
you kept hurling insults at me.
Do you remember what you said?
If only I had known sooner.
I loathe pirates.
Though I should have guessed.
That does explain your barbarism.
You're on my last nerve.
All you have to say is
help me find my body.
Asking for help from you,
pirates, I would rather die!
Yes,
but I'm sure you must pity
a poor disembodied head
who can't even defend
himself if someone attacks.
So would you like to carry me?
I'm a horrible person.
Please forgive me.
I owe you my life.
I'll never forget your kindness.
Not as long as I live.
I insulted you and your
friends, yet you rescued me.
I doubted you when you swore
to make me whole again.
And I wasn't convinced until it happened.
Forgive me.
I'm backing you.
I don't deserve your kindness.
I never should have doubted you.
What the hell are you doing?
Lift your head, you idiot.
No man should ever get
down on his knees and beg.
You got that? Yeah.
I was just thinking,
without you, I would be...
Sorry.
As much as I hate to interrupt
this touching moment, I must.
You see, it would appear that
we're in mortal danger right now.
Thanks to our colorful friend.
What's with all the slime guys?
I thought I told you to
do something about it.
Well we tried and didn't work, so we
just gave up—what were we supposed to do?
You chump, shouldn't
have given up so easily?
We've got to stop it somehow.
We all know that Nami would kill me if
anything were to happen to this body.
You are never gonna
give it back to her.
Are you, nope?
No way in hell!
If I may make a suggestion—why don't
we try to destroy it with fire?
Huh, see my blade—it burns as it cuts.
That's why I am known as Fox Fire. Keen?
Em on allow me to blaze a
path so that we may escape.
You can burn and...
can burn and Slice enemies?
Sounds a lot like magic if you ask me.
You cut through it? No way.
I've cleared our path of the slime.
I'm coming for you, Momonosuke!
How are we still alive?
I thought we were engulfed by the
fire from that massive explosion,
but I suppose not, huh?
Excuse me, Mr.
Kin'emon, if you wouldn't mind,
could you explain what just happened?
I don't mind at all.
I cut through the explosion.
And how'd you do that?
My foxfire-style slices with flame.
And through the knowledge and
use of my myriad of secret arts,
I am able to cut through flame as well.
There is no fire that can
withstand my blade. None.
Now then, Momonosuke is in danger.
I must go and rescue him.
I'll take my leave.
Hang on!
I've always wanted to
see a samurai in action.
Tell you what, Kin'emon,
I'll help you save your son.
You